payetteforward.com 2018-05-20

# Payette Forward Privacy Policy - Payette Forward

## Why Does Payette Forward Have A Privacy Policy?

In short, we’re required to have a privacy policy because we allow you to post comments using your Facebook account instead of having to create yet another account for this site. Facebook requires us to have a privacy policy, but it’s a good idea anyway.

The long and short of it is that we don’t know who you are, but we use Google Analytics to see where you’re coming from by anonymously collecting your zip code – **we don’t get any closer than that.** If you want us to know who you are, you’ll tell us. We don’t give away or sell any of your information to third-parties or advertisers or do any of that sort of thing. We only want to be helpful. Here’s a privacy policy that I made using an excellent “Privacy Policy Generator” for websites at <https://www.privacychoice.org/policymaker/>. Thanks for understanding and [Contact Payette Forward](https://www.payetteforward.com/contact) if you have any questions at all.

## Privacy Policy

 **We only collect anonymous information.  
**

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you.

In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number or email address.

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.  
**We do not store or share your precise location.  
**  
We do not use or collect your precise geographic location.  
**You can request to see your personal data.  
**  
You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, email, address or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information.  
**We keep personal data until you delete it.  
**  
We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely.  
**We don’t share your personal data with other companies.  
**  
We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies.  
**Ad companies collect anonymous data. You can opt out.  
**  
Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices:

Google

Google (www.google.com) operates the Google Display Network (comprising partner websites and some Google properties like YouTube), DoubleClick online ad serving products and the DoubleClick Ad Exchange, and Invite Media. These provide advertisers with the tools needed to plan, execute and analyze marketing programs with greater ease and efficiency, while enabling publishers to maximize their returns from online advertising.  
Note: Because Google uses DoubleClick and Invite technology, cookies placed by Google for behavioral advertising, including the opt out cookie, will appear as DoubleClick and Invite cookies.  
**You can ask privacy questions or opt-out of marketing.  
**  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
https://www.payetteforward.com/contact/ OR info@payetteforward.com

If you have given us contact information but do not want us to contact you with promotional or marketing information, you can opt-out here:

https://www.payetteforward.com/opt-out/

Please allow sufficient time for us to process your request.  
**Analytics providers access data on our behalf.  
**  
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.

Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.  
**We take steps to protect personal information  
**  
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.  
**Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
**  
To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.  
**You can review more privacy-related information.  
**  
This privacy policy was last updated on March 4, 2014. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.

## Terms of Use

Unauthorized use and/or duplication of this material without express and written permission from this site’s author and/or owner is strictly prohibited. Excerpts and links may be used, provided that full and clear credit is given to David Payette and payetteforward.com with appropriate and specific direction to the original content.
